Guide to the Harper & Row, Publishers Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series III: Arranged Series
  - Subseries III.4: Editorial Files
    - Babson, Roger
    - Bach, Richard
    - Bailey, Geoffrey (George Vassilchikov)
    - Baillie, Hugh
    - Balinskly, Benjamin & Ruth Berger (Box 73)
    - Ball, John
    - Ballard, Ernesta
    - Ballinger, Bill S.
    - Banning, Margaret Culkin
    - Barclay, Dorothy
    - Barker, Will
    - Barlow, James (Box 74)
    - Barnes, Djuna
    - Barolini, Antonio
    - Baron, Salo W.
    - Barr, N. G.
    - Bator, Francis M.
    - Baughman, U. E.
    - Baxter, Edna M.
    - Bazak Guidebooks
    - Beal, John
    - Beale, Jeremy & Alix Coleman (Box 75)
    - Beatty, Charles
    - Bell, Bernard Iddings
    - Benchley, Robert
    - Bennett, Margot
    - Benoit, Emile & Kenneth Boulding
    - Berman, Dr. Louis
    - Bernstein, Barton J.
    - Berry, Don
    - Beste, R. Vernon
    - Bilheimer, Robert S. (Box 76)
    - Billingsley, Christa
    - Black, Gavin See Wynd, Oswald
    - Blanc, Suzanne
    - Bliven, Bruce
    - Blackwood, James
    - Blom, K. Arne
    - Bodelsen, Anders
    - Boles, Paul Darcy
    - Bondi, Hermann (Box 77)
    - Boroff, David
    - Borowitz, Albert
    - Bosley, Harold
    - Boston, Robert
    - Bosworth, Allan
    - Boucher, Constance
    - Bowen, John
    - Bowie, Russell
    - Bowles, Chester
    - Boyce, Burke
    - Boyer, Merle William (Box 78)
    - Brameld, Theodore
    - Brandes, Rhoda
    - Brean, Herbert
    - Breckinridge, Mary
    - Breland, Osmond P
    - Breuer, Bessie
    - Bridges, William
    - Brinton, Anna Cox
    - Bromfield, Louis
    - Bronowski, Jacob (Box 79)
    - Brophy, John
    - Brosnan, Jim
    - Brown, John Mason
    - Brubacher, John S. (Box 80)
    - Bruckberger, Raymond Leopold
    - Brunini, John
    - Brunner, Emil
    - Buckham, John W.
    - Bulliet, Richard
    - Burke, Jackson
    - Burke and Zaloom
    - Burkhart, Roy A.
    - Burnett, John G.
    - Butler, Paul G.
    - Butterfield, Roger
    - "Ca-Cd" (Box 81)
    - Caillou, Alan
    - Calder-Marshall, Arthur
    - Calkins, Raymond
    - Calhoun, Daniel
    - Cammaerts, Emile (Box 82)
    - Campbell, Douglas
    - Capa, Cornell
    - Carmichael, Joel
    - Carr, A. Z.
    - Carr, John Dixon
    - Carr, John Dixon (Box 83)
    - Carse, Robert (Box 84)
    - Cary, Joyce
    - Casey, Robert P.
    - Caspary, Vera
    - Cassini, Igor
    - Castelot, Andre
    - Cecil, Henry (Box 85)
    - Chamberlain, Sam
    - Chang, Diana
    - Chave, Ernest J.
    - Cheetham, Nicholas
    - Chesler, Phyllis
    - Child, Charles B.
    - Chiang, Kai-shek
    - Christiansen, Arthur
    - Christie, Agatha
    - Churchman, C. West
    - Claiborne, Craig
    - Clark, Duvie
    - Clark, Glenn
    - Clark, William
    - Clift, Charmian
    - Coates, Austin
    - Complete Hunter's Library (Box 86)
    - Connell, Brian
    - Constantino, Sam
    - Cooper, Duff
    - Cores, Lucy
    - Corfman, Eunice
    - Corrington, William
    - Coughlan, Robert
    - Council on Foreign Relations
    - Courtney-Brown, R
    - Cousteau, Jacque Yves (Box 87)
    - Cowles, Virginia
    - Coyle, Kathleen
    - Craig, Dennis
    - Crisler, Lois
    - Crowell, Norman
    - Croy, Homer (Box 88)
    - Curtis Brown
    - "Da" - "Dz"
    - Dangerfield, George
    - Dannay, Frederic
    - Dart, Raymond and Craig Dennis
    - Daves, Jessica (Box 89)
    - David, Elizabeth
    - Davidson, Bill
    - Davidson, Irwin and Richard Gehman
    - Davidson, Irwin (Judge)
    - Davidson, Lionel
    - Davis-Du Bois, Rachel
    - Deighton, Len (Box 90)
    - Deiss, Joseph Jay
    - De Jong, David
    - Dekovic, Gene
    - Deland, Margaret
    - De Pury, Roland
    - Descharnes, Robert
    - Dessart, Gina (Box 91)
    - Deutsch, Albert
    - de Vere White, Terence
    - "Di"
    - Dickinson, Peter
    - Dimont, Max
    - Dohrman, Richard
    - Douglass, Donald McNutt
    - Dreyfuss, Allen
    - Drucker, Peter
    - Drucker, Peter (Box 92)
    - Dryer, Bernard V.
    - Dugan, James
    - Dulles, Allen W.
    - Dunlap, Henry A. (Box 93)
    - Dunn, Katherine
    - Duplaix, Georges
    - Dupuy, Trevor N. and R. Ernest
    - Durdin, Peggy
    - Dwight, Olivia
    - "E - Ez"
    - Eastern National Park and Monument Association
    - Eaton, Evelyn (Box 94)
    - Eckstein, Gustav
    - Eden, Anthony
    - Eddy, Sherwood
    - Egan, Cy
    - Egan, Lesley
    - Ehle, John
    - Ehrlich, Max
    - Eliason, Joyce
    - Elizur, Yuval
    - Elliot, Sumner Locke (Box 95)
    - Elliott, Osborn
    - Ellison, Valerie
    - Englehardt, N. L., Jr.
    - Ernst, Morris
    - Evans, Richard L.
    - Everyman's ark
    - "Fa-Fq"
    - "Fl-Fz" (Box 96)
    - Fadiman, Clifton
    - Fair, Ronald
    - Farb, Peter
    - Farm Quarterly
    - Feinburgh, Wilfred
    - Fennerton, William
    - Fenwick, Elizabeth (Box 97)
    - Ferguson, Walter D.
    - Fermor, Patrick Leigh
    - Ferrars, E. X.
    - Ferri, Nels
    - Ferris, Theodore P.
    - Ferris, Wally
    - Filer, Tom
    - Finletter, Thomas K.
    - Firth, Anthony
    - Fischer, John
    - Fischer, Louis (missing) (Box 98)
    - Fisher, Douglas Alan (Box 99)
    - Fisher, John
    - Fleeson, Doris
    - Fleming, D. J.
    - Fleming, Jean
    - Fleming, Peter
    - Flewelling, Ralph Tyler
    - Fordham, Winifred
    - Fosdick, Harry Emerson
    - Fox, Emmet
    - Frankau, Pamela
    - Fraser, Kathleen (Box 100)
    - Frazier, George
    - Freeling, Nicholas
    - Fromm, Bella
    - Fuertes, Louis Agassiz
    - Fuller, General J. F. C.
    - Furnas, J. C.
    - Futagawa, Yukio
    - "Ga-Gz" (Box 101)
    - Gaddis, Paul O.
    - Gallie, Menna
    - Gallup, George
    - Gamow, George
    - Garraty, John A.
    - Garve, Andrew
    - Gavin, James M. (Box 102)
    - Geelmuyden, Hans
    - Geer, Andy
    - Gehman, Richard
    - Gelb, Barbara and Arthur
    - Geld, Ellen Bromfield
    - Green, Paul F. (Box 103)
    - Gesell, Arnold
    - Gesell Institute
    - Gibney, Frank
    - Gilbert, George B.
    - Given, William B.
    - Goldfarb, Ronald
    - Good Housekeeping
    - Goodspeed, Edgar J. (Box 104)
    - Goodwin, John
    - Gorham, Charles
    - Graham, John Alexander
    - Grant, Campbell
    - Green, Martin
    - Green, Peter
    - Greenbaum, Leonard
    - Greenbaum, Wolff & Ernst
    - Greenman, Frances Cranmer
    - Griffith, Tom
    - Grisman, Arnold (Box 105)
    - Gross, Leonard
    - Grottrup, Irmgard
    - Grubb, Davis
    - Grunwald, Henry Anatole
    - Guttmacher, Alan F.
    - "H"
    - "Ha-Hz" (Box 106)
    - Hadman, Ballard
    - Hall, James B.
    - Halle, Louis J.
    - Halliday, E. M.
    - Halliday, William R. (Box 107)
    - Hallinan, Nancy
    - Hallock, G.B.F.
    - Hamilton, Floyd E.
    - Hamilton, Hamish
    - Hamilton, Virginia Van der Veer
    - Hanff, Helene
    - Hanna & McAllister
    - Hansen, Joseph
    - Hansen, Thorkild
    - Hardin, Peter (Louis Vaczek)
    - Hardy, Lindsay
    - Harling, Robert
    - Harper 125th Anniversary (Box 108)
    - Harper Prize Novel Contest, [n.p.], 1929-1946
    - " " ", [n.p.], 1947-1954
    - " " ", [n.p.], 1955-1956
    - Harriman, Averell
    - Hawes, Bess
    - Healey, Ben
    - Hearne, John
    - Heinz, William C.
    - Helitzer, Florence
    - Heller, Bernard
    - Helm, MacKinley
    - Herman, Stewart W., Jr. (Box 109)
    - Herman, Stewart, Dr.
    - Hermanovski, Egils P.
    - Hermansen, John
    - Herrmann, Paul
    - Herzog, Arthur
    - Hesburgh, Theodore M. & Howard A. Glickstein
    - Highsmith, Patricia
    - Hildick, Wallace
    - Hill, Ralph Nading
    - Hirschberg, Cornelius
    - Hobson, Francis (Box 110)
    - Hocking, William Ernest
    - Hodder & Stoughton Ltd.
    - Hodges, Henry G.
    - Hodnett, Edward
    - Hoffer, Eric
    - Hoffnung, Gerard
    - Holmes, Sam
    - Holmes, John Haynes
    - Holzman, Robert S.
    - Horizon (Box 111)
    - Horton, Walter M.
    - Howe, Helen
    - Howe, Henry
    - Howell, Frank
    - Howells, W. D.
    - Huard and Wong
    - Hughes, Richard
    - Hughes, Ted
    - Hurd, Clement and Edith (missing)
    - Hurst, Fannie
    - Hutson, Susan Hoffman
    - Hyde, William C. (Box 112)
    - Hyman, Sidney
    - "I"
    - Idyll, Clare P.
    - Iliff, Flora
    - Illustrated History of Manners
    - Industrial Relations Research Association
    - Institute of Management Sciences (Box 113)
    - Institute for Sex Research
    - Isherwood, Margaret
    - "J" (Box 114)
    - Jameson, Storm
    - Janowsky, Oscar I.
    - Janeway, Elizabeth
    - Jeffers, Paul
    - Jenkins, Rev. Daniel
    - Jepson, Selwyn
    - Jobe, Joseph
    - Joed, C. E. M.
    - Johnson, E.
    - Johnson, June
    - Johnson, Raynor
    - Johnson, Priscilla (Box 115)
    - Johnston, Eileen
    - Jones, Candy
    - Jones, Edgar DeWitt
    - Jordan, G. Ray
    - Jones, Richard
    - Joseph, Michael, Ltd.
    - Jovanovich, William
    - "K"
    - "Ka-Kz" (Box 116)
    - Kahn, Albert
    - Kahn, E. J., Jr.
    - Kahn Anthologies
    - Kahn, Joan
    - Kaminsky, Max and V. E. Hughes
    - Kaplan, Allan
    - Kappin, Fred L.
    - Kates, George N.
    - Kates, Frederick
    - Kauffmann, Stanley
    - Kaye-Smith, Sheila
    - Kean, Charles D. (Box 117A)
    - Keating, William J. and Richard Carter
    - Kelland, Clarence B.
    - Keller, Adolph
    - Keller, Morton
    - Keller, Hannes
    - Kelley, Earl C.
    - Kelley, Francis C.
    - Kelly, James
    - Kelly, Mary Blanche
    - Kelly, Thomas R.
    - Kennaway, James
    - Kennedy, Gerald
    - Kennedy, Gerald, Bishop
    - Kennedy, James W.
    - JFK, [n.p.], 1955 - 1961 (Box 117B)
    - JFK, [n.p.], 1962 - 1964 (Box 117C)
    - JFK, [n.p.], 1964 - 1967 (Box 117D)
    - RFK, [n.p.], 1959 - 1963 (Box 117E)
    - RFK, [n.p.], 1964 - 1967 (Box 117F)
    - Kessler, Milton (Box 118)
    - Kesten, Hermann
    - Kimble, George H. T.
    - King, Dr. Martin Luther
    - King, Dr. Martin Luther (Box 119)
    - King, Winston L.
    - Kiplinger, W. M.
    - Kiplinger Washington editors
    - Kirkland, Winifred
    - Kirst, Hans Hellmut
    - Kissinger, Henry (Box 120)
    - Kittler, Glen
    - Kittler, Glen D. and Hy Steirman
    - Klein, Edward J.
    - Klein, Roger
    - Klein, Morris (Box 121)
    - Knebel, Fletcher and C. W. Bailey
    - Knowles, Horace
    - Kouwenhoven, John A. and Janice Farrar
    - Kraft, Joseph
    - Krasner, William
    - Krishnamurti, J. (Box 122)
    - Kroner, Richard
    - Kuehl, Linda
    - Kuh, Katherine
    - Kurth, K. O.
    - "La-Lz"
    - Lach, Alma (Box 123)
    - Lacy, Ed.
    - Land, Myrick
    - Lanning, George
    - Large, J. E.
    - Latourette, Kenneth
    - Lawrence, James C.
    - Lay, Beirne (Box 124)
    - Lee, Lance R.
    - Leggett, Malcolm
    - Leishman, J. B.
    - Leonard, Frank
    - Lester, Muriel
    - Lewis, C. Day
    - Lewis, Edwin
    - Lieb, Frederick G.
    - Lewis, Joe
    - Leonard, Gini
    - Lesky, Louis
    - Levin, Gordon
    - Levine, Daniel
    - Lewis, Allan
    - Lewis, Thomas P.
    - Life magazine
    - Lilienthal, David (Box 125)
    - Lincoln, Miriam
    - Linder, Erich
    - Lindey, Alexander (Box 126)
    - Lindsay, R. B.
    - Linington, Elizabeth
    - Linkletter, C. M.
    - Little, Arthur D.
    - Little, Katherine Day
    - Lobsenz, Herbert
    - Longford, Lady Elizabeth
    - Loomis, Madeleine (Box 127)
    - Lord, Bette
    - Loughlin, David
    - Lolos, Kimon
    - Lowe, Arnold H.
    - Lowrey, Janette Sebring
    - Lowry, Charles (Box 128)
    - Lubell, Samuel
    - Luccock, Halford
    - Latourette, Kenneth Scott
    - Lundberg, Ferdinand
    - Lurani, Giovanni
    - Lynes, Russell
    - Lyon, Dana
    - "Ma-Mz" (Box 129)
    - "Ma-Mx" (Box 130)
    - Maas, Joachim
    - McCabe, Charles R.
    - McCague, James
    - McCall, Oswald
    - McCarthy, Joe
    - McCormick, Jack
    - McCormick, William
    - The McCoy Company
    - McCulloch, Margaret (Box 131)
    - McDermott, Geoffrey
    - MacDonald, Lachlan
    - McGinnis, Ralph
    - McIntosh, Mavis
    - MacIver, Robert M.
    - McMurry, George
    - McMurtry, Larry
    - Mademoiselle magazine (Box 132)
    - Magnus, Mayotte
    - Mahoney, Tom
    - Mais, Walter
    - Mallet, Jacqueline (missing)
    - Mannix, Dan
    - Markets of the Sixties
    - Markstein, David
    - Marsh, John
    - Martin, John Bartlow
    - Martin, John Stewart
    - Marton, George and Tibor Meray (missing)
    - Manchester, William (Box 133)
    - Manchester, William (Box 134)
    - Marquand, John (Box 135)
    - Marton, Gregory
    - Marx, Arthur
    - Mather, Kittley
    - Matsuoka, Yoko
    - Matthews, I. G.
    - Maurer, Herryman
    - Maurois, Andre
    - Maus, Cynthia Pearl
    - Maxfield, Henry S.
    - Mayer, Milton
    - Mathew, Lewis B.
    - Mazo, Earl
    - "Meditations of William of St. Thierry"
    - Meek, Howard
    - Merchant, Ismail
    - Mikes, George
    - Milburn, R. L. P.
    - Miller, George A.
    - Miller, J. Lane (Box 136)
    - Miller, O. T.
    - Miller, Samuel H.
    - Miller, Sylvia
    - Millikan, Max F. and W. W. Rostow
    - Millstein, Gilbert
    - Moffatt, James
    - Momsen, Admiral Charles and Peter Maas
    - Montgomery, Marion
    - Montross, Lynn (Box 137)
    - Mooney, Michael
    - Moore, Bruce F.
    - Moore, Raymond S.
    - Moore, Richard E.
    - Moore, Robert E.
    - Morgan, Barbara Spotford
    - Mornell, Pierre
    - Morrison, Charles C.
    - Morris, Joe Alex
    - Morrison, Charles Clayton
    - Mortier, J. and M. L. Auboux
    - Moseley, J. Rufus (Box 138)
    - Motter, Alton M.
    - Mounier, Emmanuel
    - Mowat, Farley
    - Moynihan, James H.
    - Muilenburg, James
    - Muller, Herbert J.
    - Muller, Herbert J. (Box 139)
    - Muller-Alfeld, Theodor
    - Murdock, George P.
    - Murphy, Francis X.
    - Murphy, Grace E. Barstow
    - Murray, A. Victor
    - Mydans, Carl
    - Myers, Lou
    - Myers, Martin
    - Mystery Dept.
    - "Na-Nz" (Box 140)
    - Nasby, A. Gordon
    - Nash, James E.
    - National Audobon Society
    - Nature Books
    - Neider, Charles (See also Twain, Mark)
    - Neill, Stephen
    - Nevins, Francis (Box 141)
    - New York University (Dean Thomas Norton)
    - New Yorker magazine
    - Newberry, Clare Turlay
    - Newman, James R.
    - Newman, Sally
    - Neyman, Jerzy (Box 142)
    - Nicely, Harold E.
    - Nicol, Eric and Peter Whalley
    - Nida, Eugene
    - Niebuhr, Richard
    - Nielson, Torben
    - Niemöller, Martin
    - Nikhilananda, Swami
    - Norris, Frank
    - "Oa-Oz" (Box 143)
    - O'Brien, Kate
    - Oduyoye, Modupe
    - Ogburn, Charlton
    - O'Hanlon, Sean
    - Oka, Hideyuki
    - Okrent, Danny
    - Oldham, J. H.
    - Olsen, Jack
    - O'Malley, Michael
    - "Outdoor Life"
    - Outler, Albert
    - Oxnam, G. Bromley
    - "Pa-Pz" (Box 144)
    - Pahk, Induk (Box 145)
    - Palmer, W. Scott
    - Paolotti, John
    - Papashvily, George and Helen
    - Paris Review magazine
    - Payne, Robert
    - Peace Corps. Project
    - Pearson, Hesketh (Box 146)
    - Penrose, Roland
    - Pelikan, Jaroslav
    - Peterson, Nancy
    - Pettit, Paul
    - Phenix, Philip H.
    - Phillips, Cabell
    - Phillips, Harold Cooke
    - Phillips, Thomas Hal
    - Picard, George (Box 147)
    - Pick, Robert
    - Pierce, Edith L.
    - Pierce, John R.
    - Pike, James A.
    - Pillsbury project
    - Piper, Evelyn
    - Playboy magazine
    - Player, Robert
    - Pomilio, Mario
    - Pontifex, Dom Mark
    - Ponce, Charles
    - Poteat, Edwin McNeill
    - Poteat, Gordon
    - Prange, Gordon
    - Price, Joe
    - Priestley, J. B. (missing) (Box 148)
    - Procter, Maurice
    - Prou, Suzanne
    - Prudden, Bonnie
    - Pugh, Marshall
    - "Q" (Box 149)
    - "Ra-Rz"
    - Radler, D. H.
    - Ramsay, Diana
    - Ransom, Jay Ellis
    - Ransom, Jay Ellis (Box 150)
    - Rapport, Samuel
    - Reddick, Lawrence D.
    - Reid, Clyde
    - Reinsch, J. Leonard
    - Rennie, Ysabel
    - Rhodin, Eric
    - Roberts, Myron
    - Robinson, James M. and John B. Cobb
    - Robinson, Leonard
    - Rojankovsky, Fedor (Box 151)
    - Roman, Howard
    - Roosevelt, Eleanor
    - Roosevelt, Nicholas
    - Root, E. Talmadge
    - Rosemarin, Judy (Box 152)
    - Roske, Ralph J. and Charles Van Doren
    - Ross, Glen
    - Ross, Ishbel
    - Ross, Marvin
    - Rosten, Leo
    - Roulston, Marjorie Hillis
    - Runyon, Damon (Box 153)
    - Russell, James
    - Russell, John
    - Ryan, John K.
    - "Sa-St" (Box 154)
    - "St-Sz" (Box 155)
    - St. Clair, David
    - Sampson, Anthony
    - Sanford, Agnes
    - Sauers, Donald J. and Elton Dedini
    - Saulnier, Dr. R. J.
    - Sayers, Michael and Albert E. Kahn
    - Sayers, Michael and Albert E. Kahn (Box 156)
    - Schaflander, Gerald and David Goodrich
    - Schellenberg, Walter
    - Scherer, Paul
    - Schloerb, Rolland W.
    - Schmidt, Carl
    - Schmoe, Floyd
    - Schneer, Cecil J.
    - Schuette, Walter (Box 157)
    - Scott, David H.
    - Scott, Jack
    - Scott, Thurston
    - Searls, Hank
    - Sharmen, Henry B.
    - Shaw, Charles G.
    - Shaw, Felicity
    - Sherwood, Robert E.
    - Shimer, John A.
    - Shoemaker, Samuel Moor
    - Simon, Pierre-Henri (Box 158)
    - Simpson, Howard
    - Sims, Edward H.
    - Sinnott, Edmund W.
    - Skolle, John (Box 159)
    - Slimming, John
    - Smith, Glanville
    - Smith, Robert Paul
    - Smith, Ronald Gregor
    - Smith, Shelley
    - Smith, F. G. Walton
    - Sokol, Erich
    - Southagte, W. M.
    - Spence, Basil
    - Sperry, Willard (Box 160)
    - Spiegler, Gerhard E.
    - Staack, Hagen
    - Stallings, Laurence
    - Stallings, Laurence (Box 161)
    - Stamm, Frederick Keller
    - Steere, Douglas V.
    - Stendahl, Krister (Box 162)
    - Stern, Frederick
    - Stevens, Henry Bailey
    - Stevenson, Dwight E.
    - Stevenson, Ian
    - Stevenson, J. W.
    - Stillman, Edmund
    - Stirling, Monica
    - Stockwell, Olin
    - Stokes, Anson Phelps
    - Stokes, Anson Phelps (Box 163)
    - Stoudt, John J.
    - Strabel, Thelma
    - Strausz-Hupe, Robert
    - Strax, Phillip
    - Streeter, Edward (Box 164)
    - Streit, Clarence
    - Stringfellow, William
    - Stryker, Perrin
    - Sugrue, Thomas (Box 165)
    - Sulzberger, C. L.
    - Summers, Hollis
    - Sumner, Cid Ricketts
    - Suter, John W.
    - Sutton, O. G.
    - Sweazey, George E.
    - Swiss Foundation for Alpine Research (Box 166)
    - Sykes, Gerald
    - Symons, Julian
    - "Ta-Tz" (Box 167)
    - Tantri, K'tut
    - Tasker, R. V. G.
    - Tate, Sylvia
    - Taylor, Harry Milton (Box 168)
    - Taylor, Samuel
    - Tchelitchew, Pavel
    - Teilhard de Chardin, Pierre
    - Thayer, Charles
    - Thelen, Herbert
    - Theoharis, Athan G.
    - Thomas, G. F.
    - Thompson, Charles
    - Thompson, J. Walter
    - Thurman, Howard
    - Time, Inc.
    - Tolbert, Frank X. (Box 169)
    - Toulmin, June
    - Travers, Hugh (Box 170)
    - Traywick, Robin B.
    - Trent, Robbie
    - Trevor, Elleston
    - Troebst, Cord-Christian
    - Trueblood, D. Elton
    - Tsou, Tang
    - Twain, Mark (See also Neider, Charles) (Box 171A)
    - Twain, Mark (Box 171B)
    - Twain, Mark (Box 171C)
    - "U" (Box 172)
    - UNESCO World History
    - Urwick, Lynn
    - "V"
    - The Valley by Lorus & Margery Milne
    - Van Dyke, Henry
    - Van Gulik, Robert
    - Veillon, Lee
    - Vermont Life Development Commission
    - Vining, Elizabeth Gray (Box 173)
    - von Frisch, Karl
    - "Wa-Wg"
    - "Wh-Wy" (Box 174)
    - Wainwright, Loudon
    - Walker, Harold B.
    - Wallace, Lew
    - Wallace, Paul A.
    - Wallace, Robert
    - Walles (Box 175)
    - Wallis, Charles L.
    - Walsh Chad
    - Warren, Joyce
    - Ways, Max
    - Weatherspoon, Jesse B.
    - Weber, Rubin
    - Weist, Carl S. (Box 176)
    - Wells, Thomas B.
    - Wescott, Regina H.
    - Wescott, Glenway
    - West, Dorothy
    - Wheeler, W. Reginald
    - Whiston, Charles F.
    - White, Robin
    - White, Reginald (Box 177)
    - Wicker, Tom
    - Widgery, Alban G.
    - Wiener, Daniel N.
    - Wilder, Amos N.
    - Wiley, Bell and Hirst Milhollen
    - William Morris Agency
    - Williams, Alan
    - Williams, Gluyas (Box 178)
    - Williams, Vinnie
    - Wilson, Dorothy Clarke
    - Wilson, William G.
    - Winters, Jonathan and Philip Cammarata
    - Winterton, Paul
    - Winwar, Frances
    - Winwar, Frances (Box 179)
    - Wise, Arthur (Box 180)
    - Wohlstetter, Albert
    - Wolhorn, Herman
    - Wolfe, Thomas
    - Wolfe, Winifred
    - Wolff, Leon
    - Woodfin, Henry
    - Woods, Sara
    - Woolson, Arthur
    - Wright, Andrew
    - Wright, Richard
    - Wyeth, John A.
    - Wynd, Oswald (Box 181)
    - "X-Y" (Box 182)
    - "Y"
    - Yates, Raymond
    - Yilla
    - Young, Edward
    - Young, Roland
    - "Z"
    - Zilinsky, Ursula
    - Zolotow, Charlotte
    - Zuver, Dudley
- Series IV: Business Files
  - Accepting the universe (Box 183)
  - Advances
  - Advisory Board
  - Agents party, [n.p.], June 1, 1966
  - American Book Publishers
  - American Heritage (Box 184)
  - American Heritage, [n.p.], 1961-1964
  - American Library in Paris
  - American Museum of Natural History
  - Anniversary-150th
  - Annual Report
  - Applications
  - Applications for jobs, [n.p.], 1961-1967
  - Author's League of the Writer's Guild
  - Ba - Be (Box 185)
  - Bf - Bz
  - Bantom Books, [n.p.], 1965
  - Bestseller lists and "Best Books"
  - Board of Directors I
  - Board of Directors II
  - Board of Directors (Minutes), [n.p.], 1945-1960 (Box 186)
  - Board of Directors, [n.p.], 1962-1965
  - Board of Directors, [n.p.], 1966
  - Book-of-the-Month Club
  - C, [n.p.], 1966
  - Canada File
  - Canfield "A" (Box 187)
  - Canfield "B"
  - Canfield "C"
  - Canfield "S"
  - Canfield, Mary Cass
  - Carnegie Corporation Project
  - Cass Canfield's Office Files, [n.p.], 1972-List
  - Canfield, Michael T.
  - Charlie Brown series (Box 188)
  - Chart of Accounts
  - Christmas Card List
  - College
  - College bookstores, [n.p.], 1958
  - Colophon Books
  - Conferences
  - Contracts
  - Contracts
    [Incl. government bids]
  - Conventions - exhibits (Box 189)
  - Copyrights
  - Cost Accounting Reports
  - Cowles, John Jr.
  - Cross Marketing Committee
  - Cross Marketing, [n.p.], 1/70-12/71
  - Cross Marketing
  - Curtis Publications, Inc.
  - D4 (Box 190)
  - D.I.S.C.
  - Dealer (S) - individuals
  - Defense Orientation conference
  - Destruction
  - Direct mail (Box 191)
  - Discounts
  - Distribution Plan
  - E5 (Box 192)
  - E. M. Hale
    [Current]
  - E. M. Hale
  - Editorial
  - Editorial Advisory Board, [n.p.], 1968 (Box 193)
  - Editorial Advisory Board, [n.p.], 1969
  - Editorial Advisory Board, [n.p.], 1970
  - Editorial conference notes
  - Editorial lunch
  - Editorial trade meeting
  - Editorial trips (Box 194)
  - Educational technology
  - Educational technology SCIP
  - EL-HI file
  - Emmet, Marvin and Martin, [n.p.], 1937
  - Empire State Foundation, [n.p.], 1956-1962
  - Eric
  - Executive committee
  - Exman, Eugene
  - F6 (Box 195)
  - Figures (General)
  - Figures (Trade Seasonal)
  - Fisher - Henry and Everitt
  - Fisher, John
  - Fitzhenry and Whiteside
    [Start through 1969]
  - Fitzhenry and Whiteside, [n.p.], 1970 (Box 196)
    [Including contracts]
  - Fitzhenry and Whiteside, [n.p.], 1974
  - Footnotes
  - Foreign Rights
  - Franklin book programs (Box 197)
  - Freeze, [n.p.], 1971
  - Freeze, [n.p.], 1972
  - Future trade books (List), [n.p.], 1976
  - G7 (Box 198)
  - Grosset & Dunlap Year end reports
  - Grosset & Dunlap, [n.p.], 1960
  - Guaranty Trust Company
  - "Ha" - authors file
  - Hamish Hamilton Ltd Reports, [n.p.], 1961 (Box 199)
  - Hamish Hamilton Ltd Reports, [n.p.], 1960
  - Hamish Hamilton Ltd Reports, [n.p.], 1959
  - Hamish Hamilton Ltd Reports, [n.p.], 1958
  - Hamish Hamilton Ltd Reports, [n.p.], 1957
  - Hamish Hamilton Ltd Reports, [n.p.], 1956
  - Hamish Hamilton Ltd Reports, [n.p.], 1955
  - Hamish Hamilton Ltd